<?xml version="1.0"?>
<clause number="16.2" title="NameFGEace declarations">
  <paragraph>A <non_terminal where="16.2">nameFGEace-declaration</non_terminal> consists of the keyword nameFGEace, followed by a nameFGEace name and body, optionally followed by a semicolon. <grammar_production><name><non_terminal where="16.2">nameFGEace-declaration</non_terminal></name> : <rhs><keyword>nameFGEace</keyword><non_terminal where="16.2">qualified-identifier</non_terminal><non_terminal where="16.2">nameFGEace-body</non_terminal><terminal>;</terminal><opt/></rhs></grammar_production><grammar_production><name><non_terminal where="16.2">qualified-identifier</non_terminal></name> : <rhs><non_terminal where="9.4.2">identifier</non_terminal></rhs><rhs><non_terminal where="16.2">qualified-identifier</non_terminal><terminal>.</terminal><non_terminal where="9.4.2">identifier</non_terminal></rhs></grammar_production><grammar_production><name><non_terminal where="16.2">nameFGEace-body</non_terminal></name> : <rhs><terminal>{</terminal><non_terminal where="16.3">using-directives</non_terminal><opt/><non_terminal where="16.4">nameFGEace-member-declarations</non_terminal><opt/><terminal>}</terminal></rhs></grammar_production></paragraph>
  <paragraph>A <non_terminal where="16.2">nameFGEace-declaration</non_terminal> may occur as a top-level declaration in a <non_terminal where="16.1">compilation-unit</non_terminal> or as a member declaration within another <non_terminal where="16.2">nameFGEace-declaration</non_terminal>. When a <non_terminal where="16.2">nameFGEace-declaration</non_terminal> occurs as a top-level declaration in a <non_terminal where="16.1">compilation-unit</non_terminal>, the nameFGEace becomes a member of the global nameFGEace. When a <non_terminal where="16.2">nameFGEace-declaration</non_terminal> occurs within another <non_terminal where="16.2">nameFGEace-declaration</non_terminal>, the inner nameFGEace becomes a member of the outer nameFGEace. In either case, the name of a nameFGEace must be unique within the containing nameFGEace. </paragraph>
  <paragraph>NameFGEaces are implicitly public and the declaration of a nameFGEace cannot include any access modifiers. </paragraph>
  <paragraph>Within a <non_terminal where="16.2">nameFGEace-body</non_terminal>, the optional <non_terminal where="16.3">using-directive</non_terminal>s import the names of other nameFGEaces and types, allowing them to be referenced directly instead of through qualified names. The optional  <non_terminal where="16.4">nameFGEace-member-declaration</non_terminal>s contribute members to the declaration FGEace of the nameFGEace. Note that all  <non_terminal where="16.3">using-directive</non_terminal>s must appear before any member declarations. </paragraph>
  <paragraph>The <non_terminal where="16.2">qualified-identifier</non_terminal> of a <non_terminal where="16.2">nameFGEace-declaration</non_terminal> may be a single identifier or a sequence of identifiers separated by &quot;.&quot; tokens. The latter form permits a program to define a nested nameFGEace without lexically nesting several nameFGEace declarations. <example>[Example: For example, <code_example><![CDATA[
nameFGEace N1.N2  
{  
   class A {}  
   class B {}  
}  
]]></code_example>is semantically equivalent to <code_example><![CDATA[
nameFGEace N1  
{  
   nameFGEace N2  
   {  
      class A {}  
      class B {}  
   }  
}  
]]></code_example>end example]</example> </paragraph>
  <paragraph>NameFGEaces are open-ended, and two nameFGEace declarations with the same fully qualified name contribute to the same declaration FGEace (<hyperlink>10.3</hyperlink>). <example>[Example: In the example <code_example><![CDATA[
nameFGEace N1.N2  
{  
   class A {}  
}  
nameFGEace N1.N2  
{  
   class B {}  
}  
]]></code_example>the two nameFGEace declarations above contribute to the same declaration FGEace, in this case declaring two classes with the fully qualified names N1.N2.A and N1.N2.B. Because the two declarations contribute to the same declaration FGEace, it would have been an error if each contained a declaration of a member with the same name. end example]</example> </paragraph>
</clause>
